e e
hello good morning Mr
Vu can you unmute your yeah are you
going to share this slide I'm Dr Ashley
here
from uh sir actually slide has to be
shared from your end actually as for the
discussion with don't have slides but I
think uh somebody from uh increment will
be doing it uh I have to check sir Give
Me 2 minutes sir I have to check and
just call you okay okay fine fine let me
know for
yoube
sir hi this is no actually I just have a
word with vikas he has sh he has shared
the PBT with Ravi I guess there is R
will be online is it yeah yeah yeah to
vikas is also coming and he's having a
word with the Ravi I guess the will RI
comes I'll make him the co-host and he
can share okay fair enough sir thank you
thank you so much thank you for
attending the meeting
stop live stream can end meeting
Dr Ashley you make me
host and I'll be able to share the
screen then I have got the pp from ICC
Lombard
already uh RI are you list what are you
listed as trainer RC yes yes yes okay
okay I made a co-host and I'm stopping
my share
okay how
ch
R good
morning RI good morning yeah good
morning I'm sh today only six or seven
of us are on
Zoom because problem of muting and
unmuting is there everybody else is on
YouTube
so where are rest of the People YouTube
YouTube okay so mostly people are
watching us through YouTube only
around more than 200 people watching on
YouTube now okay great great you can
start anytime you want you can
start you can see your screen now you
can
start okay vikas you can start now you
see Vias pan has joined us he must be in
the waiting room
ah yes
admitting V good morning welcome to
malod group presentation on I home
insurance re from increment is also
there you can start
ready vikas are you there
becauseas are we audible to you
please enbl the sound I think
oh yeah vikas has not uh now he's got
now he's got join audio yeah yeah yeah
I've joined RI okay thank you thank you
so I'm sharing the screen now and we can
start the session uh in Zoom session
becauseas there are just seven guys but
this training is Live on YouTube and
there are 200 plus people watching us
through YouTube okay okay okay so
welcome in the name of monal
group we havei staff on zoom and most of
our brand staff around 250 are on
YouTube you can go ahead whenever you
can yeah thanks um RI can you can you
please che check if uh venu has joined
or not yeah venu is there already we
were speaking to him already Mr
vuas I'm here only yes RI I am here only
okay okay so Mr Vishal Shasta also
entered the waiting room let me admit
him also one
second
okay yeah v g uh actually audio is not
okay V you you have joined now okay
yeah Mr
V yeah
yeah
Mr is also from I lombar team
okay let me set the contest for the
meeting yeah uh good afternoon all this
is vikas from ICC Lombard and uh uh as
of all of you know that IU Lombard is
the established brand in the the
industry and uh we are the uh
second rank overall in GI industry and
myself becauseas is working with d
Lombard since
2013 and uh Mr venu is there along with
me he is the professional trainer uh he
takes care of of all the training
sessions and Mr Vishal is also uh in the
session he uh I report to Mr Vish so Mr
venu uh over to you
yeah thank you thank you thank you uh
thank you vikas and Ravi G I guess you
would be uh accessing the slides on this
so yes yeah okay good morning friends
and uh we would be discussing on the
home insurance and home insurance is a
very basic and very very easygoing
product on with I Lombard we are
covering almost everything which which
is
which is ass with your home insurance it
would be the content or it would be the
structure I'm just giving you a bit link
access from where a customer or an
channel can log in the policy directly
and we have shared the same PP on the
slides as well so Ravi G can you please
move on the
slides okay okay thanks a lot RI I
request if you uh click on this control
l so your this PDF file will be on the
full screen contr L I'm not using laptop
but mobile phone I have no I have no
idea okay no no issues no issues there
no issues so first slide is showing that
it is a basic detail we we shared a link
for a home insurance and first when the
customer clicks on that particular home
insurance link this this page will open
this is the first page and is the entire
journey to login a home insurance policy
and uh with this journey only we will
understand which all coverages are there
and how we can opt for the coverages and
what would be the we can have the
estimated premium also there there is
one quote of Premium which has been
shared in the uh entire journey of this
home insurance PBT so first there are
basic information as I told you you have
customer has to enter his name mobile
number and email ID everything every
communication will be communicated on
this uh mobile number number and email
ID if the customer wants to get the
communication or updates of the policy
from IC Lombard through WhatsApp to he
or she can opt for this and click on
proceed RI I guess PB is not shared from
your end it has been
ched okay now now it is visible uh R
next next
slide now
okay sorry sorry R please you can go on
the previous slide okay thank you thank
you so this is the uh second when you
click on the proceed button it required
Standalone uh residence insurance policy
basically so you have to mention the
property type which would be the owned
or rented property uh the option if I go
for own property then I have to mention
the PIN code in which particular area it
is been and I have to click on
next then the other slide will be
showing it shows a property
uh owner and your PIN code will be uh
freezed which you have already mentioned
in the previous slide now you have to
opt for the you have three options here
what all you want to cover if you want
to cover only the structure structure
and you have to keep in mind the the
cost of the uh insurance we are
valuating it on the content or on the
structure the land cost will not be
included if the prop if the property
building cost is for an example 50 lakh
rupees and the land cost is because it
is in the POS area if I take an example
of Delhi only or Mumbai only so the land
cost is somewhere around five cres or
two CR Rupees to company will be giving
you the cost of structure the rebuilding
cost of that particular property so you
have to keep in mind and definitely when
you would be discussing and selling the
home insurance you have to discuss with
your customer also so customer has to
opt for three options he's having three
options either he wants to have the
structured
covered either he wants to cover the
content we will be having a overl what
what all things are covered under
content content is the things furniture
or your expensive paintings or your
jewellelry and everything which which is
inside your home so basically you can
cover that also uh second option is
content and if the customer wants to
cover both the things structure and
content he can opt for that in this
example we have taken the third option
that is structure and content and the
cost of this we as it is mentioned
excluding the land cost so what would be
the structure and content cost as per
the market price so that that has to be
mentioned here so we have taken it's 50
lakh rupees here uh and we have to click
on proceed
button G we know how would customer
decide the value of the
structure basically this structure cost
would be the market price and if
required we have certain amount on this
if required we have the surveys also
available here let me interfere here uh
I would like to throw some light on this
how customer would take a uh overall
structure uh cover uh we'll give uh the
customer to option to uh choose from
2,000 per square fet construction cost
to up to 5,000 per square fet let's
suppose if anyone anyone have has uh
flat of 2,000 square ft then customer
would choose any any Su between 40 lakh
to 1 CR that would be the construction
cost and we will BSE construction cost
only in case of any uh demise of the
property C land will be the remains at
there only there will be no
loss of
land okay continue
please and what would be the
uh bracketing of 5,000 sare ft Vias I
think you have
maximum 5,000 square ft 5,000 rupees per
square fet construction cost can be
opted okay okay fair enough fair enough
so I think vikas has addressed the query
which has been asked uh now we are
moving to the next
slide uh now it is the content value uh
what all value you want to cover and we
we have mentioned the it's having MN
option available so we have opted for
I'm having a durable and functional
equipments that cost which includes my
TV my uh my gadgets and everything uh
that uh that cost 1 lakh rupees my
furniture is costing somewhere around
20,000 10,000 rup I am taking an Habit
example here it has been just to
understand the definitely the furniture
would be more costly in the actual
scenario and jewelry cost is somewhere
around 20,000 rupees and if I talk about
the clothing utensils and the
miscellaneous items be remaining item
would be there that would be of 1 lakh
rupees so I have mentioned this my
structure and uh this cost would be 50
lakh rupees and content cost would be by
with the bation is that so next we have
to uh proceed further further for the
more details add it also from here right
yeah yeah you can this is the amount
which has been mentioned by the customer
only so you can give any any number if
you are having the furniture for an
example you are having an antique
furniture that cost somewhere around 50
lakh rupees so you can just mention that
amount this is just an example RI uh we
have given an uh option to choose the uh
choose the sum SW uh to the customer uh
customer can Avail from these options
durables and functional equipments
Furniture jewelry jewelry would be
25% of the sum is sold and five lakh
whichever is lower let's suppose
customer is choosing 50 lakhs some sort
of content in that case uh jewelry would
not be covered more than five lakh right
okay there is a cap on
J okay right and uh uh there is three
tenure available in the content part one
one year three year three year and 5
year there will be 15% discount on
threee premium and 25% discount on um
5year
premium same applicable on structure
part also there are uh five five options
of one year three year 5 year 10 15 and
20 years there would be 15% discount
applicable on threeyear
premium uh 25% discount applicable on 5e
premium 50% discount applicable on 10
year and 50% discount on 15 and 20 years
as
well right so we would show people uh
that Journey also although these are the
pictures but once we will show them
exact Journey from the application
people are using now would be easy for
them so we will cover that also after
this okay Mr Vu continue please
thank you
Ri so as we have already taken the
details of property and what would be
the subish short of the structure or the
content now the basic coverages are
there so these are the basic coverages
which which are included in
the by I will say precisely that these
are the things which can impact your
property so that would be fire
flood lightning roid strike
miscellaneous damage earthquake storm
cyclone or any kind of a terrorist
terrorist involvement or act of
terrorism would be there that would be
covered and if something happens then
there would be a loss of property or a
loss of content uh that would be uh paid
up to the limit of the suard or the
coverages which has customer has opted
under the um ICC policy
so we know even that structure can be
any Factory also is it possible
we cover only residential property
only we cover only residential property
only in this product for factory you
have to
other okay okay that comes under sure
sure for factory we have a we have a
separate this vertical that is so you
have to go with and they will they will
give you detail then that's not just the
part of this conversation no issue
continue please yeah yeah to uh uh the
these are the additional coverages if if
customer wants to add the additional
coverages so basic coverages is the
delling all risk and dwelling includes
the loss of damage due to or resulting
from the accident so if there is any
accident involved which have which we
have discussed in the previous slide so
that that comes under ding ding we would
be having some of the uh exclusions I
will say that would be if the damage
caused by a cricket ball something
happens to to your window or some some
other thing will get damaged that will
not be covered if you are transferring
some of your content I guess you you are
taking a your LED TV that cost one lakh
rupees from one room to another room and
in between it got damaged that will not
be covered and falling of the tree on
the house if something happens and tree
uh tree got fall on your place and you
incurred some of the losses that will
not be included in the dwelling piece
you have the additional coverage is also
uh you want content all risk to content
all risk also cover the all the risk
including the damage due to bugy or due
to the accident it would be covered in
that it is an additional coverages if
you want you can opt for that then we
have additional expense for the rent for
the alternative accommodation that would
be it its limit has been defined up to
the limit of two lakh rupees
or this this coverages will be when if
something some damage occurs to your
house and you would be uh staying out of
your house in in a hotel or in you have
taken a rented accommodation so that
amount will be uh taken care up to the
limit of 2 lakh rupees additional living
expenses if uh if due to the damage your
living expenses has been incurred and
you have there the cost of uh that thing
so that would be covered up to the limit
of 2 lakh
if I if I talk about the other
additional options that is the
mechanical breakdown if something
happens to the uh your the in nowadays
everything including the House locks to
the alarm system is everything is on the
electronic Gadget things and if
something happens basically on the
electrical or mechanical failure would
be there so that would be covered under
this any fin art would be there if you
would be having any intakes and uh
expensive paintings so you can take the
cover of this um personal accident if
something happens you slep in the house
or something happens like that you fall
from the roof or uh there is a there is
a fall from the stairs itself that would
be covered uh personal liability
insurance if something happens the there
is a property Dam or something happens
uh the law iner to some other uh person
on that he has uh legally uh cost
involved there so that would be covered
up to the limit of 50 lakh rupees it
includes the legal fees and all
compensation also included in this if if
removables of derable is that if you are
uh taking out of your if you have a
garden for an example and if you have a
property on the ground for and you are
uh taking out some of the remains or
waste from your property so if something
uh the cost of that will also be covered
up to the limit of uh this 10 lakh
Rupees and loss of rent if uh if
property damage occurs and you have
rented that particular property and
because of the damage your property is
now vacant and you are not getting the
rent out of that so you will be uh given
the uh benefit out of this option and up
to the limit of 2 lakh rupees so you can
you can opt for the all the option
available with the home insurance
basically the vanilla product will be
covering only dwelling all risk
coverage so now is the thing which Vias
was saying if you go for 3 years premium
you would be having a u premium discount
of uh almost 15% and if you go for a 5
years premium you would be having a
premium discount of almost uh 25% so
this is the options available with the
customer he can go up to one year policy
to 5e policy uh up to his convenience
and he can opt for that and then he has
to click on
proceed in the last slide it is
mentioned all the coverages are also
there which are covered under this
policy and your Basics some of the
structure and the premium is there when
you click on the proceed premium the
premium will be freezed you can see on
the top of left side of below the IC
Lombard logo then customer has to
reconfirm his details and he have to
mention uh he has already mentioned his
name he has to mention his date of birth
mobile number is already automatic fetch
from the previous uh slide he has to
reconfirm his email ID then he has to go
for the risk location address you have
to mention the complete address of that
particular property and location should
be selected and uh basic details should
are there in the next slide you have to
mention the uh this additional details
are there
when in
that if you want to mention some of the
details so you can you can just furnish
here and you have to accept the terms
and condition uh uh tle and after that
you can your submit button would be
activated on clicking on the submit
button you just have been redirected to
to the premium slide all the options of
online options are available RI I am on
the next
slide yeah uh so these are the payment
options which are available and these
are the normal options which are
available on the all the online portals
so you can go with the wallet or you can
credit card debit card net banking on
UPI just have to select the option and
just uh go for the payment and you will
get the
confirmation on the final page that your
transaction has been successfully
completed and you can download your
premium receipt and then and there you
will be getting your policy document and
the premium receipt on the register mail
ID which you have already mentioned in
the previous slide so this is the entire
journey of home insurance I guess it is
it is not too much lengthy it is it is a
self-explanatory and when you would be
once having the buling exess then you
will be having the confidence when you
it it is just in one one go Journey if
you have once go
the entire flow then then I think uh
nothing else would be needed to discuss
with the customer for opting for a home
insurance policy so I guess we have
completed the entire journey and yeah we
would like to show our people the
journey from the application we have
already given these guys Dr Ashley I'm
sharing the screen and sharing the Mula
mod application now and we will a little
bit explain how to buy home insurance
from the app we have already given to
all of your
people so this is the application uh
guys you can go to this application of
mulam motel and uh there is an uh Prime
product section available here and this
is ICC Lombard home insurance product
which is already there you can buy that
product from here only we have got IC
Lombard Health also which we have
already informed you last time now we
have got ICC home insurance available so
let me show the journey and Mr Vu Mr
vikas will help us to understand the
journey so we'll click on this
button once we click on the button then
as in the presentation it was already
informed you we need to put any name
here we can put test any mobile
number email ID because we are just
getting the code so no need to enter
exact details we will click on
proceed right now Mr Vu has informed us
if the property is owned my own property
then I'll click on this button if this
is rented then I'll click on this so I'm
taking example where I have this on
right and then I have to put the risk
pin code
also so I'll put it here 11018 of daily
I'll put now I'll click on next button
right so now here as Mr venu informed us
we have got three options we can cover
structure we can cover content also only
content only structure or we can cover
both structure and content right now
suppose we want to cover here both
structure and content so we will click
on this and now we need to put the
structure value
here suppose the structure value of the
property is 50 lakh so we'll put it and
then we'll click on proceed button
here like this and now we have to see we
have we can see the options of content
also we can cover our furniture also our
jewelry also clothing also and even
durables also okay so we can enter the
values of every content here
right so let me enter any value suppose
the durable and functional equipment are
of 10 lakh
Rupees Furniture cost is approximately
lakh jewelry of mine is supposed 2.5
lakh
only and clothing is of 1.5 lakh like
this so I have put the value of all C
which is there in my house right and
finally I'll click on proceed button
right all done now basic coverage
highlights means what are the coverages
which we are getting in this existing
policy fire is there flood is there
lighting is there water Riot earthquake
storm terrorism so everything is
covered so this is the beauty of the is
Lombard product they have covered each
and every uh coverage in a single
product right now addition coverages are
also there already dwelling and content
is already selected as we have chosen uh
to cover the structure of our property
worth 50 lakh and the content value of
our home is 39 lakh rupees right if we
want to add the additional coverages
which Mr Vu already informed us we can
add additional expenses for rent for
alternative accommodation so you can
speak to your client if he wants then
you just click on Plus
like this so you can select and deselect
from here if client is looking for
additional living expenses just click on
this like this so you can select any of
the additional
coverages right now if I as I don't want
to go with additional coverages my uh
choice is to simple dwelling all risks
plus content all risks so I'll click on
finally proceed to choose my
plan like this
now finally the total coverage value is
89 lakh rupees because 50 lakh rupees
value was of my structure and my content
value was 39 total is 89 lakh so
accordingly my premium of one year is
15268 rupees see it's not it's not no
it's not Co guys approximately one CR V
are just taking 15,000 bucks from
customer and he's risk-free right now
from here you can select any product if
I click on this we have two
year 1 year 15,000 2 year 30,000 3 year
39,000 4 year 50,000 5 year 59,000 if I
count 15 into 5 which is 75,000 but here
I'm paying just 60,000 because there is
a discount if I pay for entire five
years right
as I choose to go with one year I just
clicked on that and now
proceed and finally I just put the
detail of my customer
here customer date of birth from here I
need to
select like this and address of the
property I will put
here and my address if it is different
communication and mailing I can click on
no but I'm putting it as same policy
start date would be automatically
clicked there and if I have got my
property finan from someone I can click
on the financer name and finally I'll
click on I accept and submit
button and finally it will
be directed to the payment Gateway page
which Mr venu was showing us from there
on we can select any of the option to
make payment and we can immediately
within just five not more than 5 minutes
it will take and we can provide our
customer anytime from Mula mod
application home insurance policy maybe
I'll put the data which is test test
data so it's taking time so maybe that's
why it's taking time so I hope
the journey is now clear to everyone how
to do Journey from this application
right Dr Ashley anything which I have
left
please Dr Ashley we are done now any
queries from your site please ask
sir Doctor Is In operation
theater
Yi yeah
yeah Dr Ashley any query
now Doctor Is In operation theater sir
oh okay okay okay fine fine anyway so we
have explained uh whole journey of home
insurance I think uh Mr vhan I think
there was nothing which was something um
unexplainable we have yeah yeah we have
already covered yeah we have covered
every aspect of the product and uh uh I
think this is a very simple product
where we cover a structure and uh
content part and there are some
additional features like accidental and
rent for alternate accommodation and all
that so I think Vu has covered all the
things uh if any anyone has any query
please let me know and uh we'll try our
LEL Bas to uh uh give the solution no
problem as because people are mostly on
live on uh YouTube so they watching us
if there are some queries we will get
back to you anytime as you guys are
already accessible to us thank you so
much for that for the booking of this
product we have already shared the bit
link and uh you can share like on the
WhatsApp and through the mailers to all
your existing customer also and customer
will visit uh click on the bit link and
customer himself s would be able to uh
book the policy for himself right there
there should be there is uh no
interventions required from your side or
our side and yeah yeah yeah that link is
already there on the app also as you
have also seen maybe you guys had not
seen that how our app works Mr V and
yeah it's on it's on app app also but uh
the RM and everyone can spread it
through the
yeah WhatsApp and through mailers
also okay thank you thank you so much Mr
venu it was such a nice session and uh
Mr Vishal special thanks to you you
arranged this session within just two
days on our special request and on this
weekend you came and you joined us thank
you so much Vish I think thank you thank
you Mr RI thanks a lot yeah thank you Mr
vikas thank you so much
yeahi I would be happy to help you
further in this always welcome
love